[
  {
    "name": "Test",
    "pictureUrl": "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1593642532400-2682810df593?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjEyMDd9&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1350&q=80",
    "cards": [
      {
        "question": "Question 1",
        "answer": "Answer 1"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 2",
        "answer": "Answer 2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 3",
        "answer": "Answer 3"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 4",
        "answer": "Answer 4"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 5",
        "answer": "Answer 5"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Test 2",
    "pictureUrl": "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1593642532400-2682810df593?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&ixid=eyJhcHBfaWQiOjEyMDd9&auto=format&fit=crop&w=1350&q=80",
    "cards": [
      {
        "question": "Question 1",
        "answer": "Answer 1"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 2",
        "answer": "Answer 2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 3",
        "answer": "Answer 3"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 4",
        "answer": "Answer 4"
      },
      {
        "question": "Question 5",
        "answer": "Answer 5"
      }
    ]
  }
]
